export const data = [
    {
        id: 0, name: "테스트1", contents: [
            { id: 0, question: "타입스크립트1-1", answer: "파이썬1-1" },
            { id: 1, question: "타입스크립트1-2", answer: "파이썬1-2" },
            { id: 2, question: "타입스크립트1-3", answer: "파이썬1-3" },
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 1, name: "테스트2", contents: [
            { id: 0, question: "타입스크립트2-1", answer: "파이썬2-1" },
            { id: 1, question: "타입스크립트2-2", answer: "파이썬2-2" },
            { id: 2, question: "타입스크립트2-3", answer: "파이썬2-3" },
            { id: 3, question: "타입스크립트2-4", answer: "파이썬2-4" },
            { id: 4, question: "타입스크립트2-5", answer: "파이썬2-5" },
            { id: 5, question: "타입스크립트2-6", answer: "파이썬2-6" },
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 2, name: "테스트3", contents: [
            { id: 0, question: "타입스크립트3-1", answer: "파이썬3-1" },
            { id: 1, question: "타입스크립트3-2", answer: "파이썬3-2" },
            { id: 2, question: "타입스크립트3-3", answer: "파이썬3-3" },
            { id: 3, question: "타입스크립트3-4", answer: "파이썬3-4" },
        ]
    }
]